早
Morning.
今天如何  普罗科特先生
How are you today, Mr. Proctor?
看情况了
That depends.
你又给我带了个人头吗
You brought me another head?
不是
No.
不过我可能会带走一个
Thinking I might leave with one, though.
你杀了我的人
You killed my men.
你偷了我的毒品
You stole my drugs.
知道吗  没有什么比
You know, there's nothing more annoying
自以为掌控一切的老家伙更烦人了
than an old guy thinking he's still running things.
邦克  你个小傻逼
Bunker, you little shit.
你肯定认识我们共同的朋友米彻姆议员吧
I believe you know our mutual friend Senator Mitchum.
快把刀子放下  否则我用它把你的眼睛挖出来
Put that knife away before I cut out your fucking eyes with it.
米彻姆先生  你来干什么
Mr. Mitchum, what are you doing here, sir?
我来干什么
What am I doing here?
我来是因为你谋杀了我的左膀右臂
You murdered my fucking lieutenant is what I'm doing here.
先生  他在出卖我们
Sir, he was selling us out.
他是在执行命令
He was acting on orders.
你和普罗科特的吗
You and Proctor?
先生  我不明白
Sir, I don't understand.
那是因为你就是个白痴
That's 'cause you're a fucking idiot.
你们的造反到此为止
This little insurrection stops here.
听到了吗
Do you hear me?
-听到了吗  -是  先生
- Do you hear me?! - Yes, sir!
你们被这个蠢货误导了
You have been misled by this imbecile.
他杀害我们自己人的那一刻
The minute he killed one of our own...
你们就应该把他大卸八块
you should have torn him to pieces.
但也许现在是时候提醒你们  兄弟会已经
But maybe it's time to remind you that the Brotherhood
走出宾夕法尼亚的女妖镇了
goes way beyond Banshee, Pennsylvania.
你们现在是全国行动的一部分
You're part of a national movement,
有人不仅跟你们信仰一样
one that not only shares your beliefs,
而且愿意为信仰作出努力
but is willing to do something about it.
这是蒙蒂
This is Monty.
此后一切由他负责
He's gonna be running things from now on.
确保以后一切
Make sure things go smoothly
-顺利进行  -你不能来...
- from here on out. - You cannot come here--
你现在最聪明的选择
Smartest thing for you to do right now
就是闭上嘴
is shut the fuck up.
听到了吗
Do you hear me?
你们的第一也是唯一要务  就是搞定普罗科特先生的货
Your first and only priority is Mr. Proctor's delivery.
货搞定后  蒙蒂会评估分会的表现
Once that happens, Monty will evaluate the chapter,
挑选新老大
choose a new captain.
有问题吗
Any questions?
好  走吧
Okay, go on.
都走吧
Get out of here.
他会个麻烦吗
Is he gonna be a problem?
如果是  我允许你一枪崩了他
You have my permission to shoot him if he is.
黑吃黑
第四季
第八集
没想到你会来
I didn't think you'd come.
我想跟你道别
I wanted to make sure I said good-bye.
感觉好像我们总在道别  对吧
Feels like that's pretty much what we do, right?
是啊  这不是个好习惯
Yeah, it's kind of a bad habit, huh?
要去上大学了
So, college.
是啊
Yeah.
我考虑了三个月
I give it about three months.
发生了那么多事
With everything that's happened,
我不知道自己是不是能融入
I just don't know how I can possibly fit into someplace
大学那么普通正常的地方
as normal as college.
你肯定不会有问题
You're gonna do great.
我说不准
I don't know.
我觉得普通正常已经远离我了
I think normal might not be in my repertoire anymore.
你知道你这个年龄的好处是什么吗
Hey, you know what's great about being your age?
你有的是时间去想明白一些事
You got all the time in the world to figure things out.
你有时间
You do.
也会去想
And you will.
你很坚强  蒂法
You're strong, Deva.
你是个斗士
You're a fighter.
跟你母亲一样
Like your mother.
还有你父亲
And your father.
你肯定会做得很好
You're gonna do great.
而且现在我知道哪儿能找到你
And now I'll always know where to find you.
你会去找我吗
And will you? Find me?
我保证
Promise.
好
Good.
虽然你是个糟糕的父亲
You might be a shitty father,
但我也就只有你一个父亲了
but you're the only one I got left.
德克兰相信  撒旦跟他对话
So Declan believed that the Devil spoke to him.
撒旦真的跟他对话
Satan did speak to him.
好吧  所以说你也相信
Okay. So you believed it, too.
真实的事不需要你去相信
Something that's true doesn't require your belief.
这话我没有异议
Well, I guess I can't argue with you there.
你要明白  这不是他的选择
You need to understand he didn't choose this.
他是被选中的
He was chosen.
那他是怎么选人的
So how did he pick 'em?
他选择他认为纯洁的女孩
He chose girls that seemed to him to be pure.
他称之为神佑
He called them blessed.
神佑的女孩
Blessed girls.
他还想把我开膛破肚呢
Well, he did want to offer me
他应该并不认为我是神佑的吧
and I don't think he thought I was blessed.
你是意外
You were a surprise.
但我不是唯一的意外  对吗
But I wasn't the only surprise, was I?
什么意思
What do you mean?
德克兰是根据月运周期杀人的
Well, Declan was killing on a lunar cycle.
虽然不是每个月都杀  但一直是新月之时
Not every month, but always on a new moon.
-夜晚最黑暗时  -没错
- When the night is darkest. - Right.
除了
Except for...
她
her.
她是21号被杀的
She was killed on the 21st.
不是新月时  也不是满月时
Not a new moon. Not a full moon.
就是一个普通的夜晚
Just an unremarkable night.
我们自有原因
We had our reasons.
所以你也参与了吗
So you were in on it?
当然了
Of course I was.
我们一起参与的
We were in it together.
那你告诉我  为什么选她
So then tell me, why did you choose her?
丽贝卡·鲍曼
Rebecca Bowman.
她有什么特别之处  让你和德克兰
What was it about her that made you and Declan
决定打破月运周期的规律
decide to break out of the lunar cycle?
她也是意外吗
Was she a surprise, too?
我不想说话了
I don't want to talk anymore.
-最后清点了吗  -点了
- You did the final count? - Yes.
-都齐了  -很好
- It's all there. - Good.
把车开到指定地点  等我的电话
Bring the truck to the designated point and wait for my call.
随时恭候
We'll be ready.
关上
Close it up.
准备好了
We're set.
死了很多光头佬啊
That is a lot of dead skinheads.
就好像这里有炸弹爆炸了
Looks like a bomb went off in here.
知道你兄弟在哪儿吗
Any idea where your brother is?
不知道
No.
还在找他
Still looking.
你有没有觉得
You get the feeling there's
有我们不知道的事正在发生
something going on that we don't know about?
-接个电话  -好
- Excuse me. - Yeah.
我是邦克
This is Bunker.
普罗科特的世纪贩毒交易马上开始
Proctor's deal of the century is going down now.
现在太不是时候了
This is a really bad time.
抱歉  要我拖住
I'm sorry. Should I try and stall
刚坐私人飞机过来的哥伦比亚人吗
the Colombian men who just flew in on a private jet?
贩毒集团
Cartel?
如果我在意这事  应该也会这么想
That would be my guess if I cared.
天哪  你在哪里
Jesus. Where are you?
我在老机场
I'm at the old Municipal Airport.
好的  我去找你
All right, I'll meet you there.
我能看一眼吗
Can I see that for a sec?
霍普韦尔太太  我猜是你吧
Mrs. Hopewell, I presume.
布罗克
Brock?
你好
Hey.
审问怎么样
How's the interrogation going?
进行中
It's going.
你还好吗
You okay?
还好  我只是
Uh, yeah. I'm just kind of
顺一下这件事
rolling through it, you know?
顺便说一句  你是个不错的后援
You made pretty good backup, by the way.
我一直以为你是我的后援呢
Guess I always thought you were my backup.
是吗  才不是
Yeah, no.
我是来道别的
Well, I just came to say good-bye.
丽贝卡不是德克兰·博德杀的
Declan Bode didn't kill Rebecca.
什么
What?
博德是按照月相杀人的
Bode was killing on a lunar cycle.
丽贝卡的案子与其他的不同
Now, Rebecca's killing stood out
因为那天不是新月
because it wasn't on a new moon.
我逼问莉莉斯这件事
Now, I pressed Lilith about it and...
她一直闪烁其词  归根结底
she made a bunch of noise, but behind it all,
我认为她对这件事毫不知情
I don't think she knew anything about it.
也许博德没有告诉她
Well, maybe Bode didn't tell her.
不  博德打破他的规则  这不合常理
No, it doesn't make sense that Bode would break his routine.
所以呢  你是说还有一个人逍遥法外
So, what, you're saying there's someone else out there
杀害女孩  挖出她们的心脏
killing girls and then cutting out their hearts?
我是说有人杀了丽贝卡
I'm telling you that someone killed Rebecca
然后企图嫁祸给博德
and made it look like it was Bode.
他们得知道其他凶杀案的所有细节  对吧
They'd have to know details about the other murders, right?
细节还没有被披露
They haven't been released.
对  所以我们要找的人能查看警局记录
Right, so we're looking for someone who had access to BSD files
并且能够残酷地进行宗教仪式谋杀
and who's capable of a sadistic, ritualistic murder like that.
-我操  -你能想到谁吗
- Oh, fuck. - Can you think of anyone?
不如让我来说吧
Hey, maybe you should let me do the talking.
好
Sure.
他们不在家
They're not home.
我们在四周看看
Let's take a look around.
-普罗科特先生  -洛埃拉先生
- Mr. Proctor. - Senor Loera.
很高兴又见面了
Good to see you again.
我必须承认  我有点惊讶
I must admit I'm a little surprised
你竟能把这事办成
that you were able to pull this off.
我从不承诺做不到的事
I don't promise what I can't deliver.
开过来
Bring it up.
给我看看
Show me.
大家好
Hi.
我们都拿出自己的家伙来吧
As long as we all whipping our shit out...
埃米利奥·洛埃拉  是吧
Emilio Loera, I take it?
你他妈是谁
Who the fuck are you?
无名小卒
I'm nobody.
你知道我的名字  也就知道我是谁
You know my name, so you know who I am.
也就是说你明白试图偷走我的东西
Which means you know what kind of a mistake
是个怎样的错误  对吧
it would be to try to steal from me, right?
我做梦都不敢偷走你的东西
I wouldn't dream of stealing from you.
不  我来是想为你提供一项可贵的服务
No, I came here to provide you with a valuable service.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
是什么
Which is what?
我来是让你知道  普罗科特先生告诉你
I came to show you that Mr. Proctor was mistaken
你可以在女妖镇安全地
when he told you that Banshee was a safe place
发展制毒业是错的
for you to set up your manufacturing.
大错特错
Very mistaken.
如果他真的严加保管
I mean, if he had it so locked down,
我又是怎么偷到这一车毒品的呢
how did I steal this truck full of all these drugs?
-我他妈灭了你  -停
- I'm gonna fucking slit your throat. - Stop.
我想你提供的这项服务
I suppose you have some fee in mind
是要报酬的吧
for this service.
不  有时服务本身就是回报
No. Sometimes a service is its own reward.
现在让我和我的朋友离开
Just let my friend and me walk away right now
我们就扯平了
and we'll call it even.
走吧
Start walking.
你不能让她就这么走了
You're not just gonna let her walk out of here?
闭嘴
Shut up.
无名氏小姐
Hey, Miss Nobody.
你真认为我会放你走吗
Did you really think that I was gonna let you leave?
不  我没这么想
No, actually, I didn't.
对
That's right.
你的毒品被炸了
Someone just blew up your fucking drugs.
好准头
Nice shot.
谢了
Thanks.
你真的要适可而止了
You know, you really need to stop doing this shit.
-你自己来的  -我是认真的
- You invited yourself. - I'm serious.
这已经成为你的坏习惯了
It's become like a bad habit with you.
这是最后一次
This was the last time.
这话我早听过了
I've heard that shit before.
车真不错
This is a very nice car.
混蛋
Son of a bitch!
得了吧  没人真的会弄
Oh, come on. No one really knows how to do that.
只要找对力矩
It's just a matter of applying the right torque
再稍微转一转
and then a little bit of scrubbing.
是个工具房
Toolshed.
看看你
Look at you.
如果我最近学到点什么  那就是
If there's one thing I've learned lately,
总会有一个地下室
it's that there's always a basement.
在这
Right over here.
有血迹
We got blood.
是啊
Yeah.
你怎么看
What do you think?
地下室里一定没好事
I think nothing good happens in basements.
天呐
Jesus.
你那边有什么发现吗
You find anything else over there?
没有
No.
什么都没有
No, nothing.
好  那我们上去吧
All right, well, I say we head up.
我联系鉴定科  几小时就能到
I can get forensics down here in a couple hours.
我要查出血迹是谁的
I want to find out whose blood that is.
好
Sure.
我就不等他们来了  不介意吧
You mind if I don't stick around for that?
我得去看个人
I got to check in on someone.
你得去看个人
You got to check in on someone?
对
Yeah.
要人陪吗
Hey, you want or need company?
这次不用
Not this time.
-贩毒集团不会放过你的  -我知道
- The cartel will come after you. - I know.
那怎么办
And what then?
会有时间协商的
There'll be time to negotiate.
在那之前
But before then--
是你
You.
看起来断了啊
That looks broken.
你他妈的干吗
What the hell are you doing?
搞什么
Oh, what the fuck? Hey!
那是丽贝卡的项链
That's Rebecca's necklace.
对
Yes, it is.
-我不明白  -博德没杀丽贝卡
- I don't understand. - Bode didn't kill Rebecca.
你  你杀了她
You? You killed her?
在你的木屋里发现的
I found this in your shed.
-你认为我杀了她  -对
- You think I killed her? - That's right.
你他妈疯了吗
Are you out of your fucking mind?
我爱她  我愿意为她死
I loved her. I would have died for her.
-也许你爱得太深了  -什么
- Maybe you loved her a little too much. - What?
你发现她怀孕后
When you found out she was pregnant,
你意识到再也控制不了她了
you realized you couldn't control her again,
所以你把她带到那个变态的地牢
so you took her down in that weird little dungeon of yours
把她开膛破肚
and you butchered her.
你说什么  什么地牢
What the hell are you talking about, dungeon?
-是你杀了她  -你他妈的说什么
- You killed her. - What the fuck are you talking about?
你发现她怀孕了  所以杀了她
You found out she was pregnant and you killed her!
不  我没有
No! No, I didn't!
我没杀她
I didn't kill her.
糟糕
Shit.
搞什么
What the fuck?
混蛋
You son of a bitch.
他会杀了你的
He'll kill you for this.
你会来找我吗
And will you? Find me?
我保证
Promise.
我
Ev--
我所做的一切
everything I did...
都是为了你
I did for you.
放开我
Untie me!
放开我  混蛋
Untie me, you son of a bitch!
你在毁掉他
You're ruining him.
我不会再让这发生了
I can't let that happen anymore.
他爱我
He loves me.
你不明白
You don't understand.
别这样
Don't do this.
他没看透你
He doesn't see you,
但我看透了
but I do.
-我看透了你  -博登  求求你
- I see you. - Burton, please.
我看透了你
I see you!
求求你
Please.
对不起
I'm sorry.
I'm-- I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起  对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
对...
I'm-- I'm...
没关系
It's okay.
-没关系  博登  -对不起
- It's all right, Burton. - I'm sorry.
没关系
It's all right.
有什么消息吗
Did you hear anything?
还没有
Nothing yet.
-柯特  -我明白
- Kurt. - I know.
-柯特  -天呐  加尔文
- Kurt! - Oh, my God, Calvin.
玛吉  进屋去
Maggie, go inside.
你和玛吉有一腿啊
So you and Maggie, huh?
我早该预料到的
I guess I should have seen that coming.
她最爱安抚受伤的心灵
She was always a sucker for wounded birds.
你走吧  加尔文
Just walk away, Calvin.
不  我不会走的  柯特
No, I'm not going to walk away, Kurt.
我不能走  男人的忍耐是有限度的
I can't. I mean, a man can only take so much,
忍无可忍
can only swallow so much shit
无须再忍  对吧
before the time comes to address it, right?
抱歉  我没想搞成这样
I'm sorry. I didn't expect this to happen.
抱歉  为加入兄弟会抱歉
You're sorry? You're sorry you ever joined the Brotherhood?
为把我带进兄弟会抱歉
You're sorry you brought me into it?
为干了我老婆抱歉吗
You're sorry you fucked my wife?!
你就是个可悲的混蛋
You're just one sorry piece of shit, aren't you?
我会开枪的
I will shoot you.
来吧  柯特
Go ahead, Kurt.
开枪吧
Shoot me.
然后玛吉就可以无忧无虑
Then you get Maggie free and clear.
你住进我家
You can move into my house,
抚养我儿子
raise my son.
对吧  柯特
Come on, Kurt.
何必创造自己的人生  夺走我的就行了
Why build your own life when you can just steal mine?
-闭嘴  -开枪啊
- Shut up. - Shoot me.
-闭嘴  -开枪
- Shut up. - Shoot me!
求你走吧
Please just walk away.
动手吧  来啊
Do it. Go ahead.
他妈的把枪给我
Give me that fucking gun.
该死
God damn it.
可恶
Oh, shit.
玛吉
Maggie!
你们无处可逃
There's nowhere you can go,
你们都是
either of you.
我会找到你们  让你们付出代价
I will find you and I will make you pay!
就算你把我关起来  兄弟会也不会放过你们
Even if you lock me up, the Brotherhood will hunt you down.
你知道的  他们会当着她面灭了你
You know it. They will slit your throat in front of her
然后把这个贱人大卸八块
and then tear her ass to pieces.
你们无处可逃
There's nowhere you can go that we won't find you.
我就算杀了我儿子
I will kill my own son
也不会让你抚养他
before I let you raise him.
我要杀了你  贱人
I'm gonna kill you, you bitch.
只要我还活着  我
As long as I'm alive, I will...
我早知就不该
Well, I should have known better
让你那样离开
than to let you go off like that.
鉴证科那边怎么样了
How'd your forensics team do?
他们找到了些皮肤样本
They found some skin samples.
也许和普罗科特的匹配
Probably gonna match Proctor's.
其实并不是他
It turns out it wasn't actually him.
是博登
It was Burton.
博登
Burton?
对
Yeah.
戴眼镜的那个
Guy with the glasses.
他的管家什么的
His butler or whatever.
管家干的
The butler did it?
真的
Seriously?
那我应该去逮捕这个管家博登了
Well, I should probably go arrest this butler Burton, no?
对啊
Right.
早该料到
Should have guessed.
那看来我的工作结束了
Then I guess my job here is done.
对  我也是
Yeah, me too.
我也是
Me too.
是该开始新生活了
It's about time I moved on.
其实已经好几次这么打算了
It's been time a couple of times, actually.
什么时候到特区的话
Well, if you're ever in D.C....
来找我
look me up.
我会的
I will.
逮捕报告
-早上好  -谢天谢地
- Morning. - Oh, thank God.
真正的咖啡
Real coffee.
对
Yes.
-玛吉怎么样了  -她还好
- How's Maggie doing? - She's okay.
他们明晚从你那搬出来
They'll be out of your place by tonight.
不急
No rush.
看我弄清楚了没
Let me see if I got this straight.
加尔文朝你扑来  把你暴打一顿
Calvin got the jump on you, beat the shit out of you,
然后你突然想起来自己有枪
then somewhere along the way, you remember you got a gun
从六米远处打死了他
and you shoot him from 20 feet away.
对吗
Is that it?
-对  -一派胡言
- Yeah. - Bullshit.
长官  我不确定你想暗示什么  但
Sir, I'm not sure what you're trying to imply, but--
我没有暗示  我在陈述事实
I'm not implying anything. I'm saying it.
你暴打了加尔文
You beat the shit out of Calvin
然后你又杀了他
and then you killed him for good measure.
邦克  别紧张
Hey, Bunker, relax.
这里只有我们两人  明白吗
It's just you and me talking here, okay?
来  坐下
Come on, sit down.
邦克  我不明白这镇子是中了什么邪
I don't know what it is about this town, Bunker.
是什么地理现象导致我们像磁铁一样
What geographic phenomenon makes us a magnet
吸引着东密西西比的混蛋和罪犯
for every scumbag and criminal east of the Mississippi.
我只知道要做我们这份工作
But what I do know is that to do this job,
有时需要取下警章  使用一些非常手段
sometimes you've got to take off these badges and get bloody.
以前就发生过  今后还会继续
It's happened before and it'll happen again.
我需要知道我可以信赖你
And I got to know that I can trust you.
你也可以信赖我  你明白吗
And you can trust me. You understand?
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
很好
Good.
有点信任是好的
A little trust would be nice around here.
柯特·邦克是你真名吧
Kurt Bunker, that's your real name, right?
只是
Just...
普罗科特怎么办
So what about Proctor?
你可以在毒品交易现场拿下他
You can place him at the scene of the drug deal.
对  我们本可以逮捕普罗科特
Yeah, we could arrest Proctor.
但我有种感觉
But I got a feeling
贩毒集团会对他们死去的人
that the cartel's gonna want a few words with him
向他讨说法  而当他们来的时候
about their dead men, and when they come,
我希望他离警局越远越好
I'd just as soon he's as far away from the police station as possible.
-如果你懂我的意思  -有道理
- If you take my meaning. - That makes sense.
岁月积累的经验  孩子
Time and experience, son. Time and experience.
你去写那份扯淡的报告  让我签字
So, you go write up that bullshit report so I can sign it.
遵命  长官
Yes, sir.
谢谢你  长官
Thank you, sir.
谢谢你的咖啡
Thanks for the coffee.
女妖镇  建于1895年
看你的脸
Look at your face.
你就是管不住自己  对吗
You just can't help yourself, can you?
我就是这样
I gotta be me.
我明白
I know.
麦克斯明天回来
Max comes back tomorrow.
太好了
That's great.
是的
Yes.
贾伯告诉我你要去纽约
Job tells me you're heading out to New York.
对  其实是他去
Yeah. Well, he is.
我会到处看看
I'm gonna take the scenic route,
在纽约见见他
catch up with him.
你要去哪儿
Where are you headed?
不知道  我...
I don't know. I'm gonna...
我会上路后再看情况
hit the road and see what happens.
你想一起吗
You want to come?
没事
Yeah.
你要小心
You be careful.
好的
Yeah.
我会的
I will.
一直...
You know, the whole ti--
我坐牢的那些年
all those years in my cell,
你一直在我心里
you were always there with me.
我还是与你一起的
I'm still there with you.
我也会一直在这儿
And I'll always be here.
没有其他人
No one else--
没人真正了解我
nobody ever really knew me.
我懂
I know.
请不要忘了我
Please don't forget about me.
永远不会
Never.
永不
再见  安娜
Good-bye, Ana.
叫我卡莉
It's Carrie.
这车可不好找
This was a hard car to find.
是啊  抱歉
Yeah, sorry.
我借给你的时候就该想到
I should have figured that once I loaned it to you,
完璧归赵的可能几乎为零
odds were that I wouldn't be getting it back in one piece.
你打算怎么离开这儿
How you plan on getting out of here?
怎么来的就怎么离开
Same way I came in.
这里会变得很安静
It's gonna be mighty quiet around here.
别假装你会想我
Don't even pretend like you're gonna miss me.
我是在跟胡德说
I was talking to Hood.
我想我会怀念这里
You know, I think I'm actually gonna miss this place.
我不会
I know I'm not.
糖果  在这过得很开心
Sugar, it's been a thin slice of heaven.
你不是真心话
I know you don't mean that.
没错  不是
It's true, I don't.
-你很急吗  -当然
- You in a rush? - Damn right.
每次我想离开这该死的地方
Every time I try to get out of this motherfucking place,
就会有破事发生  而我会被卷入其中
some shit goes down and I get stuck in it.
我要趁能走时赶紧走
I'm getting while the getting's good.
不过在我走之前
But before I do...
我想我该把我的账单付了
figured I'd pay my tab.
这钱你哪儿来的
Where the hell did you get this?
你心知肚明
Now, you know better than to ask.
重点是你用你的退休金赎回了我
Point is, you spent your retirement fund getting me out.
你又太老做不了酒保  所以
Well, you're too old to be slinging drinks, so...
谢谢
Thank you.
你知道怎么找到我
You know how to reach me?
没人知道怎么找到你
No one knows how to reach you.
-他知道  -对  我知道
- He does. - Yeah, I do.
我该走了
This is where I leave you.
宾州女妖镇
Banshee, Pennsylvania.
去死吧
Suck my tit.
女妖镇边界  别离开太久
怎么了
What?
我想起你第一次走进这里的情景
I was just remembering the first time you walked in here.
永远都想不到
I never could have imagined.
有些人也许会说
You know, some might say you weren't all that bad
你警长当得不错
at that whole sheriff thing.
而有的人会说
Yeah, and other people might say
我是这个镇最糟糕的噩梦
I was the worst fucking thing that ever happened to this town.
你有地方住吗
You got a place to stay?
像你那样戴上警徽
Putting that badge on the way you did,
我绝对想不到你会
I never thought you'd be walking out of here
活着离开这儿
on your own two feet.
我也没想到
Neither did I.
如果不是你  我多半活不了
You know, I probably wouldn't if it wasn't for you.
你隐居在山里
You know you hid up on that mountain
因为你觉得你需要赎罪
because you felt the need to atone for something.
我们都知道  要不是布罗克找到你
And for all we know, you'd still be there
把你带回来  你还会待在那儿
if Brock hadn't come and pulled you down.
我们是罪犯
We are cons.
我们以为坐牢才是
We're made to believe that you pay for your sins
赎罪的正确途径
by getting locked up.
但也许赎罪的方式
But maybe the way to redemption
不是隐居在山里
isn't hiding on the mountain.
也许是选择另一条路
Maybe it's about choosing another road
和我们剩下的人一起走
down here with the rest of us.
也许吧
Maybe.
过去已经把你囚禁太久
The past has kept you locked up long enough.
如今你只有一个问题
Today there's really only one question
需要问自己
left to ask yourself.
你现在有什么打算
What are you going to do now?
女妖镇边界  别离开太久
[全剧终]